upi.com 2017-09-18

# About United Press International | About UPI

[Home](https://about.upi.com/) » Miscellaneous » **Privacy Policy**

United Press International (referred to herein as "UPI") recognizes the importance of protecting the information it collects from users in the operation of UPI.com, email newsletters, and other online activities. As such, UPI takes reasonable steps to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of this information. 

To enhance the user experience, UPI may ask you for information such as your name, e-mail address, year of birth, gender, zip code, country, street address, and other information that identifies a particular individual. You agree and understand that UPI may use such information in many ways, including for the following purposes 

  * to provide you with any requested information, content, goods, and/or services, whether offered by UPI or any advertisers, sponsors, licensees, or any other third parties 
  * to send you information and promotional materials about content, goods and services, whether offered by UPI or by any advertisers, sponsors, licensees or any other third parties 
  * to share your information with any advertisers, sponsors, licensees or any other third parties so that these third parties can send you promotional materials, which includes but is not limited to communications that directly promote the use of Web sites, or the purchase of products or services 
  * to customize the website according to your interests. 
  * to share with and/or sell to any successor to or purchaser of part or all of the assets of UPI. 

In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, UPI reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. UPI may also disclose this information in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics and demographics, to advertisers and other businesses and may disclose personally identifiable information when required by law, when desirable by UPI to exercise or preserve its legal rights, to enforce the Terms of Use for UPI.com, and/or anytime when UPI has received your consent. 

In order for UPI to evaluate what products and pages of the Web site are attractive to our users, UPI has entered into agreements with online partners to assist UPI in determining how visitors use the Web site. To collect this important information, UPI and UPI's online partners may use Web servers, beacons and cookies to do all or some of the following: (1) track user activity on UPI.com to generate site usage reports, (2) record registration information so the user does not need to re-enter it each time, (3) record user-specific information on what pages or other sites the user accesses or visits, and (4) record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when the users return to our site. The type of information collected includes user geographic location, which pages each user visits, ISP, GMT timeframe, referral and destination sources, as well as visit duration. This information may be disclosed to advertisers and other businesses in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics (including "hits" on UPI.com) and demographics, but only in forms that do not reveal a user's identity. UPI's online partners, who serve ads when you visit our Web site and provide other online services, may also use beacons, cookies & other tracking technologies to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you and to track how ads are displayed and which ads are clicked on. If you would like more information about these practices and to know your choices about opting out and not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Please [click here](http://teads.tv/en/privacy-policy/) to learn information on the data collection and use policies of Teads.TV, who provides video advertising services to UPI. 

Notice to EU visitors. As UPI’s operations are located in the United States, please note that if you provide information to UPI, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) to the United States. By providing information to UPI and visiting the site, you hereby consent to the storage and use of information as described herein. 

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request here. 

Please note that on UPI.com, links may be provided to other Web sites. In using such links, users should be aware that each Web site will vary in terms of its privacy and data protection policies, and United Press International does not take responsibility for the privacy policies of, and usage of, personal information collected by others. 

By accessing UPI.com, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. We may amend this privacy and data protection policy at any time. When we do amend the privacy and data protection policy, we will post the amended policy on the UPI.com site. Your continued use of UPI.com shall constitute your acceptance of such revised privacy policy. 

Any comments or questions concerning this policy please click here. If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy, (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, you may either send an e-mail by clicking here, or a written request to, Legal Department, United Press International, Inc., 1200 N. Federal Highway, Suite 200, Boca Raton FL 33432, Attn: Privacy Policy. 

Updated June 2015
